<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Star Wars Planets</string>

    <string-array name="planets">
        <item>Alderaan</item>
        <item>Cato-Neimoidia</item>
        <item>Christophsis</item>
        <item>Coruscant</item>
        <item>Dagobah</item>
        <item>Dantooine</item>
        <item>Endor</item>
        <item>Felucia</item>
        <item>Geonosis</item>
        <item>Hoth</item>
        <item>Jakku</item>
        <item>Kashyyyk</item>
        <item>Mandalore</item>
        <item>Mustafar</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="descriptions">
        <item>The homeworld of Princess Leia. Destroyed by the Death Star.</item>
        <item>Home of the Trade Federation and their unique bridge cities.</item>
        <item>A crystal planet, and the site of a fierce battle during the Clone Wars.</item>
        <item>The entire planet is one huge city. Home of the Jedi Temple and later the capital of the Empire.</item>
        <item>A planet strong with the Force, Yoda lives here in hiding as he trains Luke Skywalker.</item>
        <item>The site on an abandonded Rebel base, the Empire thought it was too remote to serve as a test for the Death Star.</item>
        <item>A forest moon, it was the site of a shield generator protecting the Second Death Star.</item>
        <item>A jungle planet, it was the site of many battles during the Clone Wars.</item>
        <item>Home of massive battle droid factories, this planet is where the Clone Wars began.</item>
        <item>A frigid ice world, the Rebels established a base here until they were descovered by the Empire.</item>
        <item>A barren and desolate planet, it was once the site of a huge battle. Only scavengers live here now. Everyone keeps trying
        to go back for some reason.</item>
        <item>A forest planet, and the location of the droid attack on the Wookies.</item>
        <item>Home to the proud and war-mongering Mandalorian people.</item>
        <item>A fiery lava planet, this is where Anakin Skywalker turned to the Dark Side.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
